<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaStr Blog ?????</title>
    <link>https://www.saastr.com/blog/</link>
    <description>SaaStr Blog????????????????</description>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:54:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Last Chance to Pitch Your AI Startup at SaaStr Annual 2025! 80+ Startups Already Slotted?Will You Be Next? (????)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/last-chance-to-pitch-your-ai-startup-at-saastr-annual-2025-80-startups-already-slotted-will-you-be-next/</link>
      <description>SaaStr Annual 2025 is set for May 13-15 in SF Bay, featuring 80 AI startups pitching on the Mayfield AI Demo Stage. Startups get exposure to 10,000+ SaaS leaders, potential investors, and buyers. The top startup stands to win $500K?$5M in funding through a SAFE investment from Mayfield. This platform allows founders to showcase their AI innovations, gain credibility, and potentially secure significant funding rounds and enterprise clients. Applications for the AI Demo Stage close on April 15, targeting founders with AI-first SaaS products or revenue-generating AI components. Even if not pitching, attending the event offers valuable networking and learning opportunities. SaaStr Annual aims to help startups scale faster and with less stress. Don&apos;t miss this chance to pitch alongside the best in AI and SaaS or be part of the event to enhance your business growth. (????)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:42:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saastr-1744396934000-</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Sell Your Startup Below the Last Round Price?  Probably.  It?s More Common Today. (????)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/can-you-sell-your-startup-below-the-last-round-price-probably-its-more-common-today/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a shift in the venture capital landscape regarding flexibility in selling SaaS businesses. It highlights the case of Loom, which was acquired by Atlassian for $975 million after its last funding round valued the company at $1.53 billion, led by Andreessen Horowitz. Despite not reaching the expected valuation, Andreessen Horowitz agreed to the sale, only getting their investment back (1x return). This example showcases a trend where VCs are showing more flexibility in selling companies at lower valuations than their last funding rounds. The article suggests that VCs are becoming more open to accepting moderate returns instead of holding out for higher valuations, especially in a market where many startups struggle to sustain their growth. This shift indicates a more pragmatic approach by VCs towards exits, focusing on ensuring some return on investment rather than risking companies stalling out. (????)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:10:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saastr-1744380626000-</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear SaaStr:  How Do I Become a Better SDR? (????)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-how-do-i-become-a-better-sdr-2/</link>
      <description>To become a better Sales Development Representative (SDR), focus on mastering your product and market to become a trusted advisor, understand target personas deeply, and write personalized, value-driven cold emails. Concentrate on creating opportunities rather than worrying about outcomes, leverage technology and data for smart prospecting, hustle with passion, and personalize your outreach to stand out. Learn from feedback, respect the role of an SDR, and keep everyone in the loop, especially founders in smaller organizations. By excelling in these areas, you&apos;ll not only improve as an SDR but also become indispensable to your team, leading to potential promotions and career growth opportunities. (????)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">saastr-1744362514000-</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>