<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaStr Blog 日本語要約</title>
    <link>https://42k310.github.io/blog-feeds/</link>
    <description>SaaStr Blogの記事を日本語に要約したフィード</description>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:11:44 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Resignations Are Up 24%. And At An All-Time High. (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/ceo-resignations-are-up-and-at-an-all-time-high/</link>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal reports a significant increase in CEO departures in 2021, with 2,221 CEOs of U.S. businesses with over 25 employees leaving, marking a 24% increase from the previous year and the highest on record since 2002. This trend is also reflected in public companies, where CEO departures hit a record high. While times were good in 2021, departures have surged since then. The article suggests that CEOs facing challenges should seek help, emphasizing the impact a great VP can have on improving the situation. The data indicates that SaaS CEOs who lead their companies to IPO tend to be founder-CEOs. This insight underscores the importance of strong leadership in navigating challenges and achieving long-term success in the SaaS industry. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:59:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/ceo-resignations-are-up-and-at-an-all-time-high/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian: “We’re Not Going to Charge More Customers Extra for AI Anymore”.  The Beginning of the End of the AI Upsell? (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/atlassian-were-not-going-to-charge-more-customers-extra-for-ai-anymore-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-ai-upsell/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the trend of AI upselling in SaaS and B2B industries, highlighting that the strategy might not be as effective as initially anticipated. Companies rushed to charge more for AI on top of existing high per seat prices, but this approach may not necessarily lead to increased deal sizes. Examples from Salesforce and Zendesk show that while AI features are being bundled or charged at higher rates, they might not significantly impact overall deal sizes. Some companies, like Monday, are offering free AI credits to attract customers. The article also mentions a perspective from Box CEO Aaron Levie, who predicts that the cost of intelligence will decrease to the cost of underlying hardware, emphasizing the potential commoditization of AI. SaaS businesses should reevaluate their AI pricing strategies and consider offering value-added services or differentiating factors beyond AI to drive growth and customer retention. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:10:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/atlassian-were-not-going-to-charge-more-customers-extra-for-ai-anymore-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-ai-upsell/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear SaaStr: How Do I Become a VP of Sales Within 18 Months? (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-how-do-i-become-a-vp-of-sales-within-18-months/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the path to becoming a VP of Sales within 18 months, a feat typically achieved in 5-6 years. Key insights include the need for a strong foundation in sales, understanding metrics, and consistently hitting targets. It emphasizes the importance of mastering the sales process, building a track record of success, and gaining leadership experience. Actionable advice includes focusing on exceeding sales quotas, demonstrating leadership potential, and seeking mentorship from successful sales leaders. It also suggests leveraging resources like SaaStr and other platforms to learn from industry experts and stay updated on best practices. Overall, the article underscores the significance of hard work, dedication, and continuous learning in accelerating one&apos;s career growth in sales leadership within the SaaS industry. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-how-do-i-become-a-vp-of-sales-within-18-months/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>