<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaStr Blog 日本語要約</title>
    <link>https://42k310.github.io/blog-feeds/</link>
    <description>SaaStr Blogの記事を日本語に要約したフィード</description>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 03:05:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>5 Interesting Learnings from Twilio at $4.7 Billion in ARR (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/5-interesting-learnings-from-twilio-at-4-7-billion-in-arr/</link>
      <description>Twilio is experiencing a notable re-acceleration in growth, with double-digit growth rates, improved Net Revenue Retention (NRR), and strong free cash flow. The company is focusing on AI, particularly in voice agents, which is proving to be a significant growth driver. Twilio is now more streamlined and concentrated on its core offerings, with increased AI integration but fewer employees. Key metrics for Twilio include:  
- $4.8 billion in Annual Recurring Revenue (ARR)  
- 12% Year-over-Year (YoY) Growth, up from 7% the previous year  
- 6% growth in new customers, totaling 335,000  
- 107% NRR, an increase from 102%  
- However, one segment is only growing by 1%  
- Annual run rate of over $700 million in Free Cash Flow  
The company&apos;s shift towards a leaner structure and enhanced focus on AI technology could potentially lead to sustained success in the long run. This data provides valuable insights for SaaS businesses, emphasizing the importance of focusing on core strengths, implementing AI strategies, and optimizing key metrics like NRR for sustainable growth. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:10:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/5-interesting-learnings-from-twilio-at-4-7-billion-in-arr/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear SaaStr:  Does A Founder Need To Sell Themselves? (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-does-a-founder-need-to-sell-themselves/</link>
      <description>In the early stages of a SaaS startup, founders should handle sales themselves as it is crucial for several reasons. Firstly, founders need to prove they can sell their product before expecting others to do so, as salespeople scale processes but don&apos;t create them. If a founder hasn&apos;t sold to at least 10 customers, there is no proven process for salespeople to scale. Secondly, handling sales allows founders to learn firsthand what works and what doesn&apos;t. By being directly involved, founders gain insights into customer objections, hesitations, and preferences, which is essential for refining the pitch, pricing, and product. This experience is invaluable and helps founders avoid flying blind when making critical business decisions. Therefore, founders should actively engage in sales to establish a solid foundation for scaling the business and ensuring its success. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 09:18:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-does-a-founder-need-to-sell-themselves/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>