<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaStr Blog 日本語要約</title>
    <link>https://42k310.github.io/blog-feeds/</link>
    <description>SaaStr Blogの記事を日本語に要約したフィード</description>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:33:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Resignations Are Up 24%. And At An All-Time High. (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/ceo-resignations-are-up-and-at-an-all-time-high/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a trend of CEO departures in 2021, with 2,221 CEOs of U.S. businesses with over 25 employees leaving their positions, marking a 24% increase from the previous year, the highest on record since 2002. CEO departures at public companies also hit a record high. The data suggests that while times were good in 2021, departures have increased significantly since then. The article emphasizes the challenges CEOs face and the importance of seeking help to navigate these difficulties. It also highlights that founder-CEOs in the SaaS industry tend to go the distance and lead their companies to IPO successfully. The key takeaway is for SaaS companies to focus on building strong leadership teams, with the right VP roles in place to drive success and growth. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:59:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/ceo-resignations-are-up-and-at-an-all-time-high/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian: “We’re Not Going to Charge More Customers Extra for AI Anymore”.  The Beginning of the End of the AI Upsell? (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/atlassian-were-not-going-to-charge-more-customers-extra-for-ai-anymore-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-ai-upsell/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the trend of AI upselling in SaaS and B2B industries. Initially, many companies tried to charge more for AI on top of existing high prices, but the effectiveness of this strategy is now being questioned. While some companies like Salesforce closed AI deals, it was noted that the AI offering was often bundled and did not significantly increase deal sizes. Leaders like Zendesk charge more for AI but also experience seat contraction due to increased AI usage and reduced human involvement, potentially offsetting any revenue gains. Some companies, like Monday, are offering free AI credits to attract customers. Box CEO Aaron Levie predicts that the cost of intelligence will decrease to the underlying cost of the technology, like GPUs, with minimal markup. This suggests that SaaS companies should focus on providing value-added AI services at competitive prices rather than solely relying on AI upselling to drive growth. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:10:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/atlassian-were-not-going-to-charge-more-customers-extra-for-ai-anymore-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-ai-upsell/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear SaaStr: How Do I Become a VP of Sales Within 18 Months? (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-how-do-i-become-a-vp-of-sales-within-18-months/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the path to becoming a VP of Sales in the SaaS industry within 18 months, a significantly accelerated timeline compared to the usual 5-6 years. Key insights include the importance of gaining experience in various sales roles, demonstrating consistent performance, and taking on leadership responsibilities early on. It emphasizes the need for a strong track record of success, ability to scale revenue, and leadership skills to be considered for a VP role in a shorter timeframe.

Actionable advice includes focusing on exceeding sales targets, consistently delivering results, and actively seeking mentorship from experienced sales leaders. Building a strong personal brand, networking within the industry, and continuously learning and adapting are also crucial for rapid career advancement in SaaS sales. The article highlights that while achieving the VP of Sales position within 18 months is ambitious, it is possible with dedication, hard work, and a strategic approach to career growth in the SaaS industry. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 09:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-how-do-i-become-a-vp-of-sales-within-18-months/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>