<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaStr Blog 日本語要約</title>
    <link>https://42k310.github.io/blog-feeds/</link>
    <description>SaaStr Blogの記事を日本語に要約したフィード</description>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:05:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>It’s 4 Years Later.  I’m Ready to Buy Your Product. (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/its-4-years-later-im-ready-to-buy/</link>
      <description>Sales is crucial for SaaS companies, but it often focuses on short-term goals like hitting monthly or quarterly targets. However, as companies grow into the enterprise space with longer sales cycles, they need to adapt to the pace expansion requires. For example, at Procore, a SaaS company for Construction with over $1 billion in ARR, it can take 3-7 years to fully expand accounts.

Sales executives and startups should understand that a prospect saying no might just mean not today, highlighting the importance of nurturing leads over time. Many potential customers are not ready to buy immediately, with only about 10% of prospects being &quot;in market&quot; at any given time. This emphasizes the need for patience and long-term relationship-building in sales strategies.

To succeed in the SaaS industry, companies should focus on understanding the longer sales cycles in the enterprise market, nurturing leads over time, and recognizing that timing plays a crucial role in closing deals. Balancing short-term targets with long-term growth strategies is essential for sustained success in SaaS businesses. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:10:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/its-4-years-later-im-ready-to-buy/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear SaaStr: What is a Good Benchmark for SaaS Revenue Per Employee by Stage? (翻訳失敗)</title>
      <link>https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-what-is-a-good-benchmark-for-saas-revenue-per-employee-by-stage/</link>
      <description>The article discusses benchmarks for SaaS revenue per employee based on different stages of growth. In the Early Stage (&lt;$10M ARR), revenue per employee is around $100,000-$150,000 due to ongoing team building and investment in growth. In the Scaling Stage ($10M-$50M ARR), the target is $200,000-$250,000 as operational efficiency starts to improve. Moving to the Growth Stage ($50M-$100M ARR), companies should aim for $250,000-$300,000 per employee, showcasing operational discipline while growing rapidly. In the Mature Stage ($100M+ ARR), the benchmark is $300,000-$400,000 per employee, with public SaaS companies typically operating in this range to stay cash-flow positive and competitive. Notable examples include Zoom and Samsara hitting $300,000 per employee at IPO, while Expensify achieved $1M per employee at IPO with a highly efficient model. The key takeaway is that as SaaS companies grow, they should focus on increasing efficiency to achieve higher revenue per employee metrics. (翻訳失敗)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 09:28:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.saastr.com/dear-saastr-what-is-a-good-benchmark-for-saas-revenue-per-employee-by-stage/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>